# **ADRIANA HEESH**

# Junior Web Developer

HTML · CSS · JavaScript · React · Ruby · Ruby on Rails · Figma

## **About Me**

With a degree in marketing, a diploma in Information Technology and experience in developing full-stack web applications, managing e-commerce and social media, I have skills in programming, graphic design, user experience and subsequently have a passion for communicative and collaborative front-end projects. I seek work that challenges my skill and gets me thinking in new ways with a sense of mentorship and camaraderie with my colleagues.

## **Education**

Diploma of Information Technology - 2020 - 2022

Coder Academy

Bachelor of Business (Marketing) - 2017

Queensland University of Technology

# **Professional Experience**

## Junior Software Engineer - Outfit

April 2022 - September 2022

While working on the delivery team at Outfit, I was responsible for building and improving new and existing mini apps called templates. New templates are built using React, styled-components and any additional packages unique to the needs of the template. The focus is on pixel perfect production and functionality to suit artwork provided by the client. I was able to really focus on growing my understanding of the intricacies of CSS in this role. Additionally I learned about developing for EDMs with an MJML template for email servers. I focused on growing my soft skills working in a client-oriented environment, with deadlines and strong team communication processes in the MarTech SaaS space.

In this role I accomplished:

- Daily standup and timeline management through Jira
- Worked closely with Customer Success and Product Owners to agree on timelines, client needs, necessary deviations and working together to optimise template builds
- Team support through 'scope review' process providing an engineers perspective on a clients builds
- Built a number of pixel perfect templates for a variety of large clients
- Tracked billable hours through Harvest
- Fixed bugs/made client requested improvements in existing templates, utilising
  GitHub for source control
- Conducted frequent code reviews of colleagues templates, and took on feedback from my peers

#### Front-End Intern - PPC Samurai

January 2022 - March 2022 (5 weeks)

While interning at PPC Samurai I gained a professional experience with the following tech stack: React, Typescript, Tailwind, React Testing Library/Jest, GraphQL, Apollo Client and GitHub, I achieved:

- Implemented incremental features like an expandable/collapsible table (using React Table) and adding multiple emails to one form input (using React Hook Forms)
- Completed an independent project to optimise onboarding to the app, managing stages using Jira to work with tickets

### Marketing Assistant - PQ Collection

January 2019 - May 2020

As Marketing Assistant I was responsible for social media and website management, including content creation, influencer relationship management and copywriting. I also assisted in campaign creation and execution across marketing channels. In this role, I

- executed a rebrand and assisted in the launch of a new website with an external agency
- created new conversions by expanding social presence into other platforms
- maintained above average conversion rates on online store
- implemented a 'Shop by Shape' filter to enhance user experience
- established Instagram and Facebook to be in the top 3 traffic sources for conversions